威尔 · 森坦斯: 我们有两个立面功能，我的天哪,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: We had our two
prong facade functions, my goodness,
他们是不是很了不起？
weren't they remarkable?
如果你还记得,
And if you remember,
我想再问一次休息前我们问过的问题。
I wanna just ask that question we asked
right before the break just one more time.
我们的澄清是什么？
Which was, what is our clarification?
我想是的，有人记得我问过的问题吗？
And I think it was, can anyone
remember one of the questions I asked?
你问是不是托德？
Was it Todd, you asked?
等等，什么会？
Hold on, what would?
是的，去吧。
Yeah, go ahead.
演讲者2: 我猜当它进入调用堆栈时？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: I guess when
that gets onto the call stack?
威尔 · 森塔斯: 是的，那个函数是什么时候被
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, when does that
function that was delayed, deferred by
附加到实现数组上的承诺对象？
being attached to the promise
object on fulfillment array?
考虑到它是自动触发运行的，那么它什么时候起作用？
When does that function,
given that it's auto-triggered to run?
是不是变得很棒了？
Does it just get great?
我的意思是它是在 JavaScript 中，那么它是直接在调用堆栈中吗？
I mean it's in JavaScript, so does it
just go straight in the call stack?
没有疯狂的想法，好吧,
No crazy to think, well,
我们需要了解我们承诺延期的规则
we're gonna need to understand
the rules by which our promise deferred
函数返回到 JavaScript 以便执行。
functionality gets back into
JavaScript in order to be execute off.
知道吗，回到 JavaScript 中的调用堆栈。
You know what, get back on to
the call stack it's in JavaScript.
回到调用堆栈以便执行。
Get back on to the call stack
in order to be executed.
我们会在这里看到。
We're gonna see that here.
让我们在这里快速重申 then 方法和功能，它是做什么的
Let's just quickly reiterate here the then
method and functionality, what does it
例如，then method and functionality to call，yeah，the then method and
say, then method and functionality
to call, yeah, the then method and
调用和完成任何我们想要运行的代码的功能将返回数据。
the functionality to call and completion
any code we want to run will return data.
响应数据必须添加到 promise 对象上
The response data must be
added on the promise object
使用 then 方法添加到 fulfillment 数组的 hidden 属性。
added using the then method to the hidden
property on fulfillment array.
Promise 对象将自动触发该数组中的附加函数运行
Promise objects will automatically trigger
the attached function in that array to run
它的输入是来自 Twitter 的 web 浏览器功能的响应数据。
with its input being the response data
from the web browser feature from Twitter.
好了我们开始吧。
All right, here we go.
让我们看看，这是我们今天要看到的最复杂的代码。
Let's see, this is the most complex
code we're gonna see today.
我们会在今天下午看到，但这是一个，我这里有三个功能
We'll see this afternoon but
this is one I have three functions here
为了我尝试和最小化代码，只是得到的核心。
in order to I try and minimize
the code and just get to the core.
但是我们需要三个人在这里，以便看到我们的规则
But we need three here in order
to see the rules by which our
异步延迟代码最终被运行。
asynchronously deferred
code ends up being run.
顺便说一下，我将在最后完成“异步”这个词的意思。
And I will, by the way, finalize at
the end what this word asynchronous means.
我现在就说。
I will say it right now.
这意味着你看到代码的时候就乱编码,
It means doing code out of
order from when you saw it,
就是那个时候。
from when it was said to be done.
所以当我们看到普通的 JavaScript 代码时，如果一行代码是 do the code,
So when we see normal JavaScript code,
if a line says do the code,
那我现在就去做。
I do it right then.
如果这行代码说做代码，那么我马上就做。
If the line says do the code,
I do it right then.
异步电动说不，不,
Asynchronous says no, no,
不，当这个功能回来的时候 JavaScript 会处理。
no, JavaScript's gonna handle when
that functionality comes back in.
当你触发浏览器功能的时候，它就会被打乱顺序
And it's gonna be out of order of
when you trigger the browser feature
开始了它的工作。
that started its work.
相关的功能会回来的时候
And the associated functionality
is gonna come back in when that
背景工作完成了。
background work is done.
我们不再有我们的，我们不能离开这行代码，直到我们已经完成
No longer do we have our, we cannot leave
this line of code until we've finished on
直到我们换到下一行。
it until we've moved to the next line.
现在我们可以得到代码，然后运行它
Now we can actually have code
that's gonna be run after
我们所有的常规代码。
all of our regular code is run.
好了，我们来看看这一切是怎么发生的。
Okay, so we're gonna see how all of
that plays out here line by line.
我们已经有了传统的 ES5和更早的设置时间的函数。
We've got our traditional ES5 and
earlier set time out with a function.
它会被扔进网页浏览器。
It's gonna be thrown down the web browser.
我们接到了两个尖头的电话。
We've got our fetch call
with the two prongs.
这边，这个代码，这个图表,
With this side, and
with this code, and this diagram,
我们将看到 JavaScript 中异步性的整个映射。
we're gonna see the entire map
of asynchronicity in JavaScript.
好了，开始了，伙计们。
Okay, here we go, folks.
我们几乎已经到了最后的关卡。
We're almost at the final hurdle.
不完全是。
Not quite.
开始了。
Here we go.
第一行，我们要把什么存进我们的全球记忆里，我的朋友马特？
Line one, into our global memory we
are going to store what, my friend Matt?
讲者2: 功能显示。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: The function display.
威尔句子: 很好，功能就是威尔句子: 展示，就是这样。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Excellent, the function
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Display, there it is.
保存到全局内存中。
Saved into global memory.
谢谢你，马特。
Thank you Matt.
现在到托德下一行。
Now to Tod next line.
演讲者2: 打印 hello 功能。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: The function print hello.
威尔 · 森特斯: 打印你好。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Print hello.
存储在全局内存中，并且很好地声明和存储在内存中。
Stored in global memory as well
declared and stored in memory.
下一句 Ryan 我们该怎么做才安全？
Next line, Ryan,
what's it safe for us to do?
清除300毫秒的函数块或
Clear the function block for
300 milliseconds or
300毫秒一个区块30毫秒。
300 milliseconds a block for
30 milliseconds.
我想把这些片段剪切超过300毫秒。
I'd like to cut these bits for
over 300 milliseconds.
就是这个。
There it is.
这是一个300毫秒的新块。
That's a fresh block for 300 milliseconds.
就是这个。
There it is.
现在事情变得有趣了。
And now things get interesting.
现在我们进入设定的暂停时间。
Now we get to our set timeout.
它在 JavaScript 中做了什么有趣的事情吗，各位？
Is it doing anything interesting
in JavaScript, people?
讲者二: 没有。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: No.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 不，不是，这是唯一的问题之一。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: No, it's not,
this is one of the one-problem ones.
实际上，让我们把我们的网络浏览器放在这里，就在这里。
Actually, let's put up our web
browser over here, right over here.
网页浏览器。
Web browser.
我们已经知道，white 是 JavaScript 引擎和特性。
We've got,
white is JavaScript engine and features.
然后你看这里，我们有网络请求
And then you've got over here
we have network requests
是内置在 c + + 中的浏览器特性之一，绝对不是在 JavaScript 中。
was one of the web browser features built
in C++, definitely not in JavaScript.
而且它是通过这个神奇的 fetch facade 函数从 JavaScript 中控制的。
And it's controlled from within JavaScript
by this amazing fetch facade function.
然后我们有了控制台。
Then we had console.
我们还有计时器，网络的一个特性
We also had timer, a feature of the web
浏览器由设定的暂停时间控制。
browser controlled by set time out.
但是有一大堆我们认识的。
But there's a whole
bunch of those we know.
好了，这下面的东西都在运行
Okay, so everything below here is going
不是 JavaScript 而是我们的网页浏览器特性。
to be not JavaScript but
our web browser features.
我还忘记了我们的主平台上还有什么？
What else have I forgotten
from our main platform?
Dan，我忘记了我的主要 Java 平台是什么？
Dan, what am I forgetting from
my sort of main Java platform?
我的演讲者2: 我最喜欢的名字是 stack。
My-
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: My favorite called stack.
威尔 · 森特斯: 是的，不觉得堆栈很酷。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah,
don't feel very cool stack.
没错，就是这样。
Exactly, there it is.
就是这样，我们正在执行全局代码。
There it is.
And we're executing code in global.
就是这样。
So there it is.
不是什么好货色。
Well, not cool sack.
好的，进入 JavaScript 执行，我们已经讨论过了
All right, into JavaScript
execution we've gone we've had on
在保存全局内存时显示打印 hello 块，时间为300毫秒。
display print hello block for
300 milliseconds at saving global memory.
现在我们点好了，想说话的请举手
Now we hit okay, raise your hand if
you wanna be the person who verbalizes
伊森已经是这方面的专家了也许我们会选伊森。
through, Ethan's been already our expert
on this, maybe we'll choose Ethan.
这是第一个用言语表达的
That verbalizes through this first
立面函数设置超时时间。
facade function set time out.
如果想成为动员者请举手,
Raise your hand if wanna be the person
who mobilizes through this,
因为我没有四处看，我真的不知道。
cuz I'm not looking around,
I can't really tell.
但我看不到马特在那儿。
So, but I can't see Matt there.
马特，告诉我怎么回事。
Matt, tell me what's happening.
任何人举手都很棒，谢谢。
Anyone has raised a hand fantastic,
thank you.
但唯一让她生气的人。
But the only person that she feels mad.
因为我背对着他。
Given my back was turned.
所以，是的，马特，设置超时，它的后果是什么？
So yeah, Matt, set timeout,
where's its consequence?
演讲者2: 它将会转到 web 浏览器功能，计时器功能。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: It's gonna go to the web
browser feature, the timer feature.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 太棒了，太棒了。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Fantastic, fantastic.
网页浏览器功能。
Web browser feature.
音箱2: 它会发送持续时间，值为0。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: It's going to send it
the duration, the value of zero.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 非常好。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Very nice.
扬声器2: 还有运行打印 hello 的功能。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: And
the function to run print hello.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 好的，非常好。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: All right,
that was excellent.
这是非常好的沟通，谢谢你。
That was very well communicated,
thank you.
没错。
Yeah, exactly.
这就是我们的零毫秒。
There's our zero milliseconds.
这就是我们的功能，在完成之后运行。
And there's our function to
run on the completion of that.
那么，让我们更准确地说，现在，我们要增加的功能,
Well, let's be more precise nowadays,
our function to add to,
扬声器2: 调用 stack。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Call stack.
调用栈扬声器2: 回调队列
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: The call stack
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Callback queue
Will Sentance: 回调队列到
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Callback queue up to
0毫秒完成的回调队列。
the callback queue on the zero
millisecond completion, exactly.
那么我们设置一个计时器。
So let's set up a timer.
就是这个。
There it is.
计时器，0毫秒。
Timer, zero milliseconds.
各位，在零毫秒完成任务。
Complete at zero milliseconds everybody.
讲者二: 对。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: True.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 是的，没错，是的。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, exactly, yeah.
完成后，我们希望运行什么？
On completion,
what What do we want to have run?
我们想在 JavaScript 中加入什么，托德？
What do we wanna have taken
back into JavaScript, Todd?
演讲者2: 打印你好。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Print hello.
Will Sentance: 打印 hello，刚好在0毫秒完成
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Print hello, exactly
at zero milliseconds is it complete
就像你们说的那样？
as you all said?
当然了。
You bet it is.
完成了，计时器完成了，我们要叫它
It is complete, the timer on
completion we're going to call
印刷，他们应该只是告诉他们去从前面的怪物
Print, they should just tell them
go to go from front of monsters
如果我现在移动到它的前屏幕上。
if I'm currently moving on
the front screen of it.
不冷静。
No cools.
就是这个。
There it is.
你好。
print hello.
会在那一刻出现，但我们现在就把它放上去。
is going to be at that moment but
let's put it up right now.
我们现在就把它放上去。
Let's put it up right now.
酷。
Cool.
威尔 · 森塔斯: Que。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Que.
在这里，回调队列。
There it is, call back queue.
所以在零毫秒时，它就完成了。
So at zero milliseconds, it's complete.
Jeff，调用栈上的打印 hello 函数会怎么样？
Jeff, what's going to happen to that
print hello function on the call stack?
威尔 · 森坦斯: 不，回调队列。
&gt;&gt; [INAUDIBLE]
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: No, callback queue.
太棒了，杰夫。
Excellent Jeff.
在零毫秒。
At zero milliseconds.
没错。
Exactly.
毫秒。
Milliseconds.
我们会有《你好》杂志。
We're gonna have print hello.
我肯定它马上就会跑起来，对吧？
I'm sure it's gonna get to run almost
like almost immediately, right?
是的。
Yeah.
这么快就把那些很酷的东西发给我。
Send me all that cool stuff so soon.
我们得到的是非常认真和渴望在这里。
We got is very earnest and
eager down here.
可以人格化了。
It's ready to go anthropomorphized.
功能是非常兴奋的。
Function is very excited.
我等不及了。
It's almost I can't wait.
准备进入调用堆栈。
Ready to go off onto the call stack.
设置超时工作是在设置计时器和后台时间时完成的
Set timeouts job was done when it set up
the timer and the background time his job
是因为它将打印机的 low 函数放在回调队列中。
is done because it put the printer
low function in the callback queue.
美丽的呼喊对每一个说话的人说非常好。
Beautiful shout out to everybody
who verbalized says very nice.
现在我们来看看最难对付的家伙
We now plow on to the The toughee
我们要以毫秒的速度继续前进。
we area gonna plow on
to at one millisecond.
尽可能保持整洁。
And try to keep it as neat as possible.
用一毫秒的时间来解决这个问题。
Plow into it one millisecond.
左手边的伊森，我们在下一行做什么，左手边？
Left-hand side Ethan, what are we doing
in the next line, left-hand side?
说话人2: 声明常量未来数据。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Declare
the const future data.
未来数据，就是这个,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: futureData, there it is,
futuredata.
futureData.
这是一个双管齐下的门面。
It is a two-pronged facade.
不，不是的，它会有我们接电话的结果,
No it's not, it's going to have
the result of our fetch call,
它的 JavaScript 结果。
its JavaScript consequence.
作为未来数据的值，因为获取外观函数的获取调用,
As the value of future data, because that
fetch call, that fetch facade function,
获取 facade 功能是一个双管齐下的 facade 功能。
that fetch facade function is
a two-pronged facade function.
在浏览器中查看网络请求，在 JavaScript 中查看内容。
Look network request in the web
browser and stuff in JavaScript.
让我们来看看 JavaScript 的结果。
Let's look at it stuff in
JavaScript consequence.
所以我们要打电话给 fetch。
So we're gonna call fetch.
就是这样，我们只有一个字符串，而 JavaScript 只有一个字符串。
There it is, with our just a string,
by the way to JavaScript is just a string.
有没有人把他的数据
Is there anyone that's
taken his data down to
让浏览器变得更有意义？
the browser that it
becomes more meaningful?
到底是什么？
What exactly is it?
推特推特网。
Twitter twitter.com.
我们只是稍微缩短一下。
We're just going to shorten it slightly.
对，就是这样。
Yeah, there we go.
好的，这是 JavaScript 的结果，Dan 的 JavaScript 结果是什么？
Okay, it's JavaScript consequence, is what
Dan what's his JavaScript consequence?
它创造了一个新的承诺。
It creates a new promise.
是的，立即返回，因此存储在左边
Yeah, exactly returns out immediately,
which therefore gets stored on the left
在这一毫秒的时刻，一个物体，特殊的物体。
hand side in this one millisecond
moment an object, special object.
承诺对象，这将被存储在未来的数据中。
Promise object, and that's gonna be
stored over here in future data.
什么是意志句子: 自动的
And what are
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: The automatic
上面有房产吗 Dan？
properties on it, Dan?
说话人2: 它的价值和意愿句子: 未完成的是,
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Its value and
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Unfulfilled which is,
这是一个正好是一个数组的数组，现在是一个空数组，但
which is what a array of exactly
an array right now an empty array but
这将是一个函数的数组衍生从做得好说。
it will be an array of function
spawned from done well said.
就是这个。
There it is.
他们去数组，他们值属性，让我们不要忘记。
They go to the array and
they value property and let's not forget.
该值属性一旦更新就会立即更新
That value property is soon
as it's updated, immediately
将触发存储在该数组中的函数自动运行。
is going to trigger the function stored
in that array to automatically run.
非常好，这是因为如果我们，顺便说一下。
Very nice, which is because if we,
and by the way.
我有一种感觉，这个价值属性将会紧密联系在一起
This value property here I have a feeling
is going to be intimately connect
另一个后果，另一个刺
with the other consequence,
the other prong
从获取，这是对网络在网络浏览器中的对话。
from fetch which is speaking to
the network in the web browser.
一旦完成，返回给响应对象的值
And as soon as that's done, that value
that comes back the response object as
凯拉把它放在前面，将要填写这个值属性
Kayla put it earlier,
is going to fill in that value property
回到 JavaScript，它会自动触发任何函数
Back in JavaScript which is going to
trigger automatically any functions in
这个值作为函数的输入的数组，或者这些函数。
that array with that value as the input
of that function, or those functions.
好的，太好了。
All right, perfect.
现在让我们把手交给另一个我的上帝，让我们现在处理另一个取物的尖端。
Let's now hand to the other my God,
let's now handle the other prong of fetch.
蓝色的笔，是浏览器的东西。
Blue pen, it's web browser stuff.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 那么，请提醒我们，布雷登，什么是网络
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: So, just remind us,
Brayden, what is the web
浏览器的特性。
browser feature that
gets sort of turned on.
讲者2: 网络请求。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Network request.
网络请求。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Network request.
非常好。
Well done exactly.
网络请求。
Network request.
就是这个。
There it is.
它来了，它来了，它来了网页浏览器,
down it comes, down it comes web browser,
我们开始吧，威尔 · 森特斯: 我最好的姿势,
here we go,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: My best posture,
网络请求。
network request.
好了，我们走吧。
All right, there we go.
这不是一个大厅通行证的谈话。
It wouldn't be a hall pass talk.
就是这个。
There it is.
现在，我们要求，我们需要什么信息，亚当，在后面？
Now, we request, what info do we need for
it, Adam, at the back?
对于那个网络请求我们需要什么信息？
What info do we need for
that network request?
讲者2: 地址。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: The address.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 是的，我们有两部分感兴趣的内容。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yep,
we've got two parts of interest.
有人想告诉我吗，布雷登？
Anyone wanna tell me, Brayden?
讲者二: 域名 威尔 · 森坦斯: 域名
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Domain.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: The domain name
及-讲者二: 名录。
and-
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Directory.
威尔 · 森特斯: 是的，另一部分，确切地说,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah,
the other part of, exactly,
我们想从中获取数据的部分。
the portion of it we wanna get data from.
所以 domain 是 Twitter.com，path 是 / will / 1，默认是 get。
So domain is Twitter .com,
path is /will/1, and it defaults to get.
所以在大约1毫秒的时候,
And so at roughly 1 millisecond,
我们开始前往，我们在哪里做这个？
we start heading off to,
where shall we do this?
也许嗯，我们认为任何我猜下降到立方体非常小。
Maybe Hmm, we thought any off I
guess down to cube very small.
去推特的总部，推特的总部，看看那个，远远的。
To Twitter's headquarters,
Twitter's HQ, look at that, far away.
就是这样，一条打招呼的信息，我需要一些新的消息,
There it is, with that of a message
saying hello, I need some new tweets,
所以那些推特。
so those tweets.
我们发送的时间大约是。
And we send that off at roughly.
零毫秒。
Zero milliseconds.
真漂亮。
Beautiful.
就是这个。
There it is.
在那个时候它是完整的吗？
And is it a complete at that point?
数据拿回来了吗，丹？
Do we have the data back, Dan?
不，我们知道我们不想把它放在那里。
No, we know we don't want
put exactly there it is.
但是当它完成时，疣举起你的手。
But when it is complete,
warts Raise your hand.
你想告诉我接下来会发生什么。
You want to tell me what's gonna happen.
回到 JavaScript，在 JavaScript 中我们自己的补全是什么？
Back in JavaScript, what's our own
completion back in JavaScript?
他要给你看一个比萨饼。
He was going to show you a pizza please.
返回的对象被输入到数据的 value 属性中。
The returned object is entered into
the value property of your data.
非常非常好。
Very, very nice.
我们要保持它的简单，只是说一个字符串，实际的 tweet 本身，但
We're going to keep it simple and just say
a string, the actual tweet itself, but
是的，没错。
yeah, exactly.
这将会填充因为
That's going to go and fill in the Because
未来的数据是我们存储取冷的另一个后果的地方。
future data is where we stored the other
consequence of the fetch cool.
这个问题在 JavaScript 中产生了影响，让我们能够跟踪
It's problem that has an effect in
JavaScript that lets us keep track
和我们在后台做的事情一致。
consistently with what we're
doing in the background.
我喜欢。
I love that.
看看这种一致性，在幕后做一些事情。
Look at that consistency,
doing something in the background.
前景中有一个漂亮的承诺对象,
Got a nice promise object
in the foreground,
在 JavaScript 中保持跟踪。
in JavaScript to keep track of it.
你知道吗，它会更新它的 value 属性，当背景
You know what, it's going to be updated
its value property when the background
工作完成了，就像彼得说的那样。
work complete, just as Peter said.
所以未来的数据，你的价值
So future data, your value
就是背景调查的结果
will be whatever comes back
from the background work, but
一毫秒的背景工作还远远没有完成。
that background work at one
millisecond is so far from being done.
想象一下，如果我们不得不在 JavaScript 的前台等待它，或者
And imagine if we had to wait for
it in the foreground in JavaScript, or
我们会在那儿坐上一会儿，大概转动70毫秒。
we'd be sitting there for while,
probably turning 70 milliseconds.
我们的语言是非常务实的，但相反。
And our language would be very pragmatic,
but instead.
顺便说一句，干得好，大家我们几乎完成了所有的东西相对来说,
By the way, well done everybody we almost
finished all the fetch stuff relatively,
舒服地。
comfortably.